# TAO DUONG KHAC

# Junior Backend Developer

0977-948-802 | tao.duongkhac@gmail.com | github.com/khactao27

#### PERSONAL SUMMARY

I'm a junior backend developer (Nodejs). I have web application development experience as a Nodejs backend developer. Future goal to become DevOps engineer. I have major interests in blockchain, bigdata, internet of things. New things are what I am interested in learning. Passionate about learning new technologies. I want to connect people around me who are passionate about technology and guide new technology in the future. I like football, listening to music, coins,... I like to work with clear goals and plans. I hate broken promises.

## **EDUCATION**

## Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Engineer of Computer Engineering

• GPA: 3.85 - Semester 20202

• CPA: 3.15

## Phuong Son High School

Student

Ha Noi, Viet Nam Aug 2018 - Present

Bac Giang, Viet Nam Aug 2015 - Aug 2018

Nov 2021 – Present

Dong Da, Ha Noi, Viet Nam

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Backend Developer - Nodejs

THANG LONG TCD CO., LTD Company

- Ecommerce Project.
- Business Analystic.
- System Design Software.
- Deployment using Docker tool.
- BA for ERP project.
- Website: https://samngoclinhvietnam.vn, https://antoanthucphamhanoi.vn

#### Intership Backend Developer - Nodejs

July 2021 – Oct 2021

PPCLINK company

Ba Dinh, Ha Noi, Viet Nam

- Learning dependency injection programming technique Microservices Architecture Software.
- Nodejs, Express framework, Software System Design.
- Build backend for Chat module timnha24h application using MQTT protocol, some other service in timnha24h application.
- Deployment using Docker.

# Social Network - Web Development project

Jan 2021 – May 2021

Hanoi University and Science and Technology

Hai Ba Trung, Ha Noi, Viet Nam

- Social network web application.
- Build backend: Nodejs, ExpressJs framework, Sequelize ORM, MySQL.
- Front-end: HTML, CSS, JS, ejs engine.
- Github: https://github.com/khactao27/Social\_Network.git

## Phone store retail - Web Development project

Hanoi University and Science and Technology

- Online web for retailing phone.
- Build backend: Nodejs, ExpressJs framework, Sequelize ORM, MySQL.
- Front-end: HTML, CSS, JS, pug engine, Bootstrap.
- Github: https://github.com/khactao27/ProjectI.gitt

Aug 2020 - Oct 2020

Hai Ba Trung, Ha Noi, Viet Nam

## LANGUAGES

## English

• TOEIC: 500+

• Basic Comunication

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

Progamming languages: Javascript, Java, Python.

Platform: Nodejs. Frameworks: ExpressJs. Front-End: HTML, CSS, JS.

Database: NoSQL (Mongodb - Mongoose(ODM)), SQL (MySQL-Sequelize - ORM), Key-Value (Redis).

Message Queue: RabbitMQ, Kafka.

Developer Tools: WebStorm, Android studio, Visual Code.

Deployment tools: Docker (Docker-compose).

System caching: Redis.

Operation System: Ubuntu, Windowns. BigData: Spark, Hadoop, ETL, ELT.

Internet of Things: IoT protocol, ESP 32 MicroChip.

System Design: Microservices architecture, Layered architecture, Event-driven architecture.

## CONTACT INFORMATION

**DoB**: 02/07/2000.

Address: 74 Ngo Trai Ca, Truong Dinh, Hai Ba Trung, Ha Noi, Viet Nam.

Phone number: 0977-948-802. Email: tao.duongkhac@gmail.com

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/KTee.27

Github: https://github.com/khactao27

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tao-duong-khac-85b9a3213

#### REFERENCES

## SAN DUONG KHAC

**Designation**: Project manager.

Company: EUP TECHNOLOGY JOINT STOCK COMPANY.

**Contact**: 0976-005-150.

Relationship: Project manager, Brother.